liberkey.com 2011-03-10

# Legal Disclaimer - Privacy Policy

Legal Disclaimer - Privacy Policy   
  
By visiting this site, you confirm and acknowledge having read and accepted these terms and conditions of use.

**The Liability of Publisher**

Essential SARL can not be held responsible for any damages, direct or indirect, arising from the use of this website.  
The user is solely and entirely responsible for any direct or indirect damage, material or immaterial, resulting from its own fault caused to Essential SARL or any third party using the website or service related.  
Essential SARL can not be held responsible for acts beyond its control, such as but not limited to: failure of network access, hacking, data loss, etc..  
Essential SARL can not be held responsible for any links contained in its website to other websites, especially the advertising links.

**Privacy**

The site does not collect personal information when you visit.  
Cookies are used, however (without being indispensable and may be disabled in Web browsers) to facilitate navigation and access to certain features of the site such as but not limited to: language interface, synchronization with on-line catalog , etc.  
The site offers the opportunity to register as a user. It is thus possible to use the forum. Other features, associated with this record, may appear gradually.  
All user information is only intended for internal use of Essential SARL. They are not transmitted to third party. The user can access and modify data directly from the site (your details). The user may request deletion of his account by the contact form.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (which does not include your name, address, email address etc.) about your visits to this site and other websites to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

Third-party cookies can be used by advertisers on the site LiberKey.com  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Jurisdictional provisions**

The site and its contents are governed by French Law and any disputes relating thereto shall be subject to the jurisdiction of French courts.

**How to contact us**

Should you have any question or concerns about this Legal disclaimer and privacy policy, please use our [contact form](http://www.liberkey.com/en/contact.html).

Essential SARL retains the ability to freely modify these terms and conditions.
